{"data":[{"question":"If you ________ the instruction, read them again.","a":"don't understand","b":"didn't understand","c":"hadn't understood","d":"wouldn't understand","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Condition type I: If + simple present, simple future tense","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"I ________ it unless I had seen it with my own eyes.","a":"will not believe","b":"would not believe","c":"would not have believed","d":"would not have believe","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Unless can use in conditional sentence likes \"if\": \n- Type 3: Would\/could\/should + have+ pp, unless + Past perfect.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"Fred ________ it unless he had your permission.","a":"will not do","b":"would not do","c":"would do","d":"wouldn't have done","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Unless can use in conditional sentence likes \"if\": \n- Type 2: Would\/could\/should + Verb, unless + simple past tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"I ________ that job even if the manager offers it to me.","a":"don't accept","b":"will not accept","c":"would not accept","d":"didn't accept","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Conditional \u00a0type I: If + simple present, simple future tense\/simple present tense.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"I was reluctant ________ a decision without ________ all the facts.","a":"to make \/ to know","b":"to make \/ knowing","c":"making \/ to know","d":"making \/ knowing","answer":"2","explain":"\n- It's adj + To Verb.\n- Without + noun\/verb-ing.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"The man was accused of ________ private property.","a":"to steal","b":"stealing","c":"stolen","d":"b & c are correct","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Be accused of doing sth.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"After we ________ all our exercises, we went to the cinema.","a":"completed","b":"has completed","c":"has been completing","d":"had completed","answer":"4","explain":"\n- After + past perfect tense, simple past tense.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"None of us ________ such a delicious meal like this.","a":"taste","b":"tastes","c":"tasted","d":"has tasted","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Present simple tense: express general fact.\u00a0\n- Subject (none of) is singular.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"The country is very ________, so travelling on the road is difficult.","a":"mountain","b":"mountain-high","c":"mountain-side","d":"mountainous","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Very + adj\/adv.\u00a0\n- To be (is) + adj.","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"},{"question":"The teacher streaked the need for regular ________.","a":"attend","b":"attendant","c":"attendance","d":"attender","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Adj + noun.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"18","subcategorylv2":"26","type":"1"}]}